For the development of the musculoskeletal system, and more specifically, what
運動器系の発達、より具体的には、
we are going to see now, are the vertebrae.
これから見ていくのは椎骨です。
Do not forget that this segmentation is given.
この分節化があることを忘れないでください。
We see that there will be trajectories for the axial skeleton, the ribs, and the extremities.
軸骨格、肋骨、四肢には軌道があることがわかります。
The skeleton, the consequence of the establishment of my notochord,
骨格は、私の脊索の配置の結果として、
induces the establishment of what I call the neural tube.
私が神経管と呼ぶものの配置を誘発します。
This neural tube
この神経管は、
will gradually align itself along the longitudinal axis and organize the vascular system.
徐々に縦軸に沿って配置され、血管系を組織します。
Retention field, the differential growth rate becomes anterior.
保持の歌、差動成長速度が前方になります。
Behind, the movement does this.
後ろでは、動きはこれを行います。
So I have an aspiration field along the entire...
だから、私は全体に沿って吸引場を持っています...
which happens like this, you see, that's where I have my segmentation.
このように行われます、ほら、そこに私の分節化があります。
The anterior part will create what is called the ectodermal ring.
前方部分は、外胚葉リングと呼ばれるものを作成します。
It's epiblast, okay?
それは上胚葉です、いいですか？
It's a tissue that forms...
それは...という組織です。
all around like this, which is a ring in that direction,
このように周囲全体に、この方向のリングであり、
relative to me, and then it flexes like this.
私に対して、そしてそれはこのように曲がります。
And it is actually the flexion that creates this ring.
そして、このリングを作成するのは、実際には屈曲です。
So I have a tissue that is denser anteriorly.
だから、私は前方に密度の高い組織を持っています。
Thus, the consequences of the ventral curvature is the ectodermal ring.
したがって、腹側湾曲の結果は外胚葉リングです。
And this ring will lead to a whole series of changes
そして、このリングは一連の変化を引き起こします。
with the curvature for the organism.
湾曲とともに、生物のために。
This flexion brings about the phase of embryonic delimitation.
この屈曲は、胚の境界設定の段階をもたらします。
Here I have my tube.
ここに私の管があります。
I have my neural crests, not only is it there but it also does all of this and
私の神経堤はそこにあるだけでなく、これらすべてを行い、
it is this movement
そして、この動きは、
here of the ectodermal ring that will provide very important information
ここにある外胚葉リングの動きが、私の脊索に非常に重要な情報を提供します。
towards my noto
私の脊索に、
chord, so you see it's this compression and it does this and it comes like this I will find myself
だから、この圧縮を見てください、そしてそれはこれを行い、そしてそれはこのように来ます、私はここに、
find myself here with a movement that is induced towards my
私の脊索に向かって誘発される動きを見つけるでしょう。
The notochord is the developmental movement.
私の脊索は、発達の動きです。
here by this
ここにあるこの
which forms a system around my notochord, which we will call the
私の脊索の周りにシステムを形成するものが、椎間板と椎体の発達と呼ばれるものになります。
development of my intervertebral disc and the vertebral body.
椎間板と椎体の発達。
This entire system will begin to separate; the superior part will form the disc
このシステム全体が分離し始め、上部は椎間板を形成し、
and the part below and above will begin to form the body.
そしてその下と上の部分は体を形成し始めます。
But it is merely induced by my notochord and reorganized by, this time, the
しかし、それは私の脊索によって誘発され、今回は、導かれた私の神経堤のシステムによって再編成されます。
system of my neural crest, which is guided.
導かれた私の神経堤のシステムによって。
The notochord?
脊索？
it is the remnant and your nucleus pulposus; that way, it will give you context.
それは痕跡であり、あなたの髄核です、そうすれば、あなたは状況を把握できます。
Initially, it is the same tissue.
最初は同じ組織です。
Initially, I have vascular information,
最初は血管の情報があり、
and afterwards, I have the metameric information from the neural crest.
その後、神経堤の分節情報があります。
So, you see, I have the neurological information.
つまり、神経学的情報があるわけです。
And it is this neurological information that will separate the upper and lower parts
そして、この神経学的情報が、分子誘導によって上部と下部を分離し、
by molecular induction, which will lead to the formation of a disc.
それによって椎間板が形成されます。
With the establishment of my notochord, we have the movement.
脊索が配置されると、動きが生じます。
The induction that occurs around it, the nucleus pulposus will remain,
その周囲で誘導が起こり、髄核が残ります。
it is the axis around which the sclerotome will form.
これは、硬化節が構築される軸です。
The notochord induces the formation of the vertebral bodies from the
脊索は、体節から来る硬化節から椎体の形成を誘導します。
sclerotome which originates from the somites.
つまり、脊索は椎体と椎間板の形成を誘導するということです。
So that means that the notochord will induce the formation of the vertebral body
椎体と椎間板の形成を誘導します。
Whereas everything around it, meaning the entire arch up to the spinous process,
一方、その周囲のすべて、つまり棘突起までのすべての弓は、
That is induced by my notochord, and everything around here will be
これは脊索によって誘導され、その周囲のすべては
induced by my neural tube.
神経管によって誘導されます。
So, on a vertebra, two types of information.
したがって、椎骨には2種類の情報があります。
If I consider the spinous process, I have direct information from my neural tube.
棘突起を見ると、神経管からの直接的な情報があります。
If I consider the disc system, it is information about the notochord that induces the system.
椎間板系を見ると、脊索が系を誘導する情報です。
The notochord will induce the formation of the vertebral bodies, which originates from the sclerotome,
脊索は、硬化節から来る椎体の形成を誘導しますが、
while the neural tube will undergo formation.
神経管は形成を形成します。
from the surrounding mesoblast.
それを囲む中胚葉から。
Two different types of information.
2種類の異なる情報。
In the complete formation, there is the formation of my neural tube,
完全な形成では、神経管の形成があり、
you see, by my notochord.
脊索によって、ほら。
This will lead to a movement like this.
これはこのように動くことになります。
We suddenly see all the so-called migration,
突然、すべての移動、いわば、
the arrangement of the somites to form my sclerotome
硬化節を形成するための体節の配置が、
around the neural tube and around my notochord.
神経管の周りと脊索の周りに。
Two types of information.
2種類の情報。
Here, it will be essential.
ここでは、これが不可欠になります。
Specifically, the sclerotome to form the vertebral body; here, we will say it is a type of sclerotome
特に、椎体を形成するための硬化節、ここでは、椎弓と棘突起を形成するための
of mesoblastic type to form the vertebral arch and the spinous process.
中胚葉性の硬化節の一種であると言えます。
If you consider this, either you position yourself relative to your neural tube, and then we will have
ここで、神経管に対して自分を置くか、そうすると、
the formation of my entire arch,
私のすべての弓の形成があり、
or I will position myself relative to my central notochordal line,
あるいは、私の中心的な脊索線に対して自分を置くか、
and I will have the vertebral body.
そうすると、椎体があります。
One on the longitudinal plane, the other on the transverse plane.
一方は縦方向の平面で、もう一方は横方向の平面です。
We see the entire movement here.
ここではすべての動きが見られます。
And here, we still have this vertebral body that will form differently,
そして、ここには、まだ異なる形で形成される椎体があります。
with yet another important level, which will be the neural crest level.
avec encore un autre niveau important qui sera le niveau de la crête neurale.
This, we will do in practice; it's how we will palpate the body.
Ça, on va faire dans la pratique, c'est comment on va toucher le corps.
We will position ourselves either at the level purely of the neural tube to form this entire posterior arch,
On va se mettre soit sur le niveau purement du tube neural pour former tout cet arc postérieur,
or we will position ourselves on the longitudinal axis to work on the vertebral body,
soit on se mettra sur l'axe longitudinal pour travailler le corps vertébral,
or we will place ourselves in another plane to work on the migration of the neural crest.
ou bien on va se remettre dans un autre plan pour travailler la migration de la crête neurale.
The entire vertebra is being outlined simultaneously.
J'ai tout le vertèbre qui se dessine en même temps.
On top of that, there is the skin, there is the neural tube, and there is my notochord.
Là-dessus, il y a la peau, il y a le tube neural et il y a ma notte-corte.
Each one, I send out small molecules.
Chacun, j'envoie des petites molécules.
I am the notochord; I will be responsible for forming the vertebra.
Moi, je suis la notte-corte, moi je vais m'occuper pour former la vertèbre.
Bring me the material.
Amène-moi le matos.
At the level of the neural tube, I will initiate inductions,
Au niveau du tube neural, ok, moi je vais donner, je vais prendre, je te donne des inductions,
I will be responsible for forming the vertebral arch and spinous process.
moi je vais m'occuper pour former l'arc et l'épineuse.
And then, once this is established, where ossification begins,
Et puis au moment où j'ai ça, où ça commence à s'ensifier,
thereupon,
là-dessus,
this then provides the specific induction for my neural tube
d 'un  coup  ça  donne  l 'induction  spécifique  pour  mon  tube
and to state, 'Okay, I will now initiate'
neural  et  dire  ok  moi  maintenant  je  lance
the entire program for my nerves to ultimately form what are known as dermatomes,
tout  le  programme  pour  mes  nerfs  pour  former  finalement  ce  qu 'on  appelle  les  dermatomes
which
qui
will be segmented throughout the body, associated with what are termed dermalgias. If
seront  segmentés  sur  tout  le  corps  avec  ce  qu 'on  appelle  des  dermalgies  si
you present with a dermalgia on
tu  as  une  dermalgie  sur
a dermatome, the corresponding viscus should be examined. If multiple dermalgias are present
un dermatome il fallait voir le viscère si tu as plusieurs dermalgies
on a single dermatome, one must consider examining the corresponding vertebra.
sur  un  même  dermatome  il  faut  penser  à  aller  voir  la  vertèbre
For instance, here in dermalgia 9, I
par  exemple  ici  dans  la  dermalgie  9  je
observe within this dermalgia a positive skin rolling test, and a densification that
me  retrouve  ici  avec  dans  cette  dermalgie  un  palpé  roulé  et  là  j 'ai  une  densification  qui
appears, corresponding to the gallbladder. Proceeding, I note another one here that
apparaît  qui  correspond  à  la  vésicule  biliaire  j 'avance  tiens  j 'ai  une  autre  ici  qui
corresponds
correspond
to the pancreas, which is also indurated, and centrally, I identify what is termed the pyloric system.
au  pancréas  aussi  qui  a  duré  et  au  centre  j 'ai  ce  qu 'on  appelle  le  système  pylorique
If I have all
j 'ai  les
three manifesting during my palpation,
trois qui apparaissent dans mon palpé
I would then prioritize examining the corresponding vertebra.
je vais aller voir plutôt ma vertèbre.
If only one distinct manifestation appears,
Si j'en ai une qui apparaisse, bien nette,
I will consider examining the organ.
je vais penser à aller voir l'organe.